<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" media="screen" href="/~d/styles/rss2full.xsl"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" media="screen" href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~d/styles/itemcontent.css"?>
<rss xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/" xmlns:feedburner="http://rssnamespace.org/feedburner/ext/1.0" version="2.0">

<channel>
	<title>KnightNews.com</title>
	
	<link>http://knightnews.com</link>
	<description>UCF news, UCF football, University of Central Florida, tuition coverage, Knights football, Greek Life, online student newspaper</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 17:54:06 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=3.5.2</generator>
		<atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" href="http://feeds.feedburner.com/KnightNews"/><feedburner:info uri="knightnews"/><atom10:link xmlns:atom10="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" rel="hub" href="http://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/"/><feedburner:emailServiceId>KnightNews</feedburner:emailServiceId><feedburner:feedburnerHostname>http://feedburner.google.com</feedburner:feedburnerHostname><item>
		<title>UCF Baseball Sweeps the Siena Saints in Opening Weekend</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/KnightNews/~3/3FXLNtLVkLg/</link>
		<comments>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/ucf-baseball-sweeps-the-siena-saints-in-opening-weekend/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 17:54:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Tyler Graddy</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Baseball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Joe Marotta]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Kam Gellinger]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Siena Baseball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Tommy Williams]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ucf baseball]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://knightnews.com/?p=57748</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[ORLANDO, Fla. – The Knights completed a three game sweep in their opening weekend on Sunday, winning their closest game of the series 9-6 following victories of 8-1 on Friday night and 11-4 on Saturday. The victory on Sunday came after a weekend of domination for UCF, who is dealing with serious roster turnover after [...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>ORLANDO, Fla. – The Knights completed a three game sweep in their opening weekend on Sunday, winning their closest game of the series 9-6 following victories of 8-1 on Friday night and 11-4 on Saturday.</p>
<p>The victory on Sunday came after a weekend of domination for UCF, who is dealing with serious roster turnover after bringing in over 20 new faces to the team.</p>
<p>Freshman Robby Howell got his first start in the last game against Siena, and was able to maintain his composure through the first three innings with ease before suffering through a tough 4 run fourth inning. Howell was able to pitch himself out of the jam, finishing the inning but not taking the mound again after that. Over the 4.0 innings pitched, the newcomer struck out 2, walked 1 and allowed 8 hits.</p>
<p>It was the offensive prowess that served as the Knights’ saving grace and stable platform this weekend, however. Kam Gellinger and Tommy Williams absolutely tore the cover off the ball, combining for eleven hits – five of them for extra bases – two homeruns, seven RBIs and two stolen bases. The two of them were the only players on the roster this weekend to either hit a homerun or steal a base.</p>
<p>Gellinger began his Knights’ career Saturday night with a towering fly ball that had just enough carry it over the right field wall.</p>
<p>“Honestly, I thought it was a pop fly when I first hit it,” said Gellinger after Game 2. “Then I saw it carrying…. And carrying.”</p>
<p>The at bat was a decisive statement about the third baseman’s approach with the bat, preluding an almost perfect weekend. In eight trips to the plate he drew a team leading three walks, racked up four hits, drove in three runs, scoured four himself, stole a base, hit both a triple and a homerun. His only blemish was reaching first base on a fielding error at sort. Not once was he unable to make a contribution on offense, always finding ways to produce.</p>
<p>Even after missing the first game, Gellinger leads the team in walks, slugging percentage, runs scored and on base percentage. It was a highly impressive first impression in a season where everyone is scrapping to solidify their role on this fresh-faced team.</p>
<p>Tommy Williams was the only other Knight to take Siena deep this weekend, launching a homerun to left field in the eighth inning of Sunday’s finale; effectively hammering the nail into Siena’s coffin. Williams is off to a hot start of his own after amassing three RBIs Sunday night, hitting above the .500 mark and leading the team in total bases with 12.</p>
<p>Equally impressive was junior college transfer Joe Marotta, pitching in relief for UCF on Saturday night. Marotta was only given five batters to face – but struck out three, walked one and enticed a groundout with the other.</p>
<p>“Whatever the situation, whatever Coach Rooney wants me to do, I’m gonna do it – bottom line. I thrive on that, I want that spotlight” said Marotta.</p>
<p>A craftsman on the mound with nasty breaking stuff, Marotta leaned heavily on his slider Saturday night while keeping everyone he faced utterly off-keel. Coming off a season in which he had 91 strikeouts in a mere 87.1 innings pitched, look for him to continue his aggressive style from the bump all year.</p>
<p>The Knights will continue the long season ahead in Gainesville on Tuesday night, facing a UF team who is 2-1 after a series against Maryland this weekend. The game is scheduled for a 7 pm start.</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/KnightNews/~4/3FXLNtLVkLg" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/ucf-baseball-sweeps-the-siena-saints-in-opening-weekend/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/ucf-baseball-sweeps-the-siena-saints-in-opening-weekend/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Strongest Teen in the World is a UCF Student | Video</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/KnightNews/~3/uhbywevOkWw/</link>
		<comments>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/strongest-teen-in-the-world-is-a-ucf-student-video/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2014 02:25:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Jake Rakoci</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Glide 1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nate mccoole]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[strong]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UCF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ucf news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[weightlifting]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://knightnews.com/?p=57738</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The strongest teenager in the world is a UCF student. Nate McCoole, a 19-year old political science major at UCF, set an all-time teen record at his recent meet, lifting a total of 2073 pounds in bench press, squat and deadlift. Split apart, McCoole benched 502, squatted 772 and deadlifted 800. KnightNews.com got a chance [...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The strongest teenager in the world is a UCF student.</p>
<p>Nate McCoole, a 19-year old political science major at UCF, set an all-time teen record at his recent meet, lifting a total of 2073 pounds in bench press, squat and deadlift. Split apart, McCoole benched 502, squatted 772 and deadlifted 800.</p>
<p>KnightNews.com got a chance to catch up with McCoole in his natural environment at the UCF Rec and Wellness Center, where he also works. Check out the interview:</p>
<p><iframe src="//player.vimeo.com/video/86860686" width="500" height="281" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>Check out this video him at his recent competition:</p>
<p><iframe width="560" height="315" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/8uPlVYkcRI8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/KnightNews/~4/uhbywevOkWw" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/strongest-teen-in-the-world-is-a-ucf-student-video/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/strongest-teen-in-the-world-is-a-ucf-student-video/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: Avalon Park Man Dead in Deputy-Involved Shooting</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/KnightNews/~3/JmtAiiacYc4/</link>
		<comments>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/report-avalon-park-man-dead-in-deputy-involved-shooting/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2014 22:33:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Jacob Sadowsky</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Beyond UCF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Glide 1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[avalon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[avalon shooting]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UCF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ucf news]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://knightnews.com/?p=57721</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[An Orange County deputy shot and killed a suicidal man threatening to hurt family members, News 13 reports. According to News 13, deputies arrived at a home on Perdido Drive off Avalon Park Boulevard Sunday, responding to a call from the man&#8217;s wife saying her husband was threatening suicide. Deputies told News 13 that the [...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>An Orange County deputy shot and killed a suicidal man threatening to hurt family members, News 13 reports. </p>
<p>According to News 13, deputies arrived at a home on Perdido Drive off Avalon Park Boulevard Sunday, responding to a call from the man&#8217;s wife saying her husband was threatening suicide.</p>
<p>Deputies told News 13 that the suspect came out of the house with a shot gun, and that&#8217;s when a deputy shot him. Deputies believe the man had taken about 20 Xanax pills, according to News 13. </p>
<p>The man was 47 years old. No deputies were hurt in the incident. Continue to check back for more on this breaking news story. </p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/KnightNews/~4/JmtAiiacYc4" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/report-avalon-park-man-dead-in-deputy-involved-shooting/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/report-avalon-park-man-dead-in-deputy-involved-shooting/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>UCF Edges USF 75-74, Snaps Nine Game Losing Streak</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/KnightNews/~3/8DAJSzP4d5U/</link>
		<comments>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/ucf-edges-usf-75-74-snaps-nine-game-losing-streak/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 23:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Jake Rakoci</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Basketball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Isaiah Sykes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ucf basketball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ucf news]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://knightnews.com/?p=57716</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Isaiah Sykes had a monster afternoon in Tampa, scoring 27 points including a shot with less than 2 seconds to play that gave the Knights the lead and ultimately the victory. Sykes scored 21 of his 27 points in the second half, helping the UCF Knights(10-13, 2-10) snap a nine game losing streak and avenge [...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Isaiah Sykes had a monster afternoon in Tampa, scoring 27 points including a shot with less than 2 seconds to play that gave the Knights the lead and ultimately the victory.</p>
<p>Sykes scored 21 of his 27 points in the second half, helping the UCF Knights(10-13, 2-10) snap a nine game losing streak and avenge their home overtime loss against the Bulls earlier this season. Sykes had help from Tristan Spurlock who had 16 points to go with eight rebounds and Justin McBride added 13.</p>
<p>USF&#8217;s Victor Rudd had 21 points and nine rebounds for the Bulls (12-14, 3-10), but it wasn&#8217;t enough to give the Bulls a victory.</p>
<p>The game included seven ties and 10 lead changes, including three en route to a 38-34 halftime lead for the Bulls.</p>
<p>The Knights are back in action on Feb. 19 at home with a 7:30 p.m. tipoff against Cincinnati.</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/KnightNews/~4/8DAJSzP4d5U" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/ucf-edges-usf-75-74-snaps-nine-game-losing-streak/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/ucf-edges-usf-75-74-snaps-nine-game-losing-streak/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Safety Top Priority After Student Mugging</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/KnightNews/~3/jNeInRPplYo/</link>
		<comments>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/safety-top-priority-after-student-mugging/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 22:35:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Alex Perez</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Cat 1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Crime]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[knights pub]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pistol]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[robbery]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UCF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ucf news]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://knightnews.com/?p=57707</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Two UCF students were jumped and robbed while walking home from Knight&#8217;s Pub early Wednesday morning. Josiah Devine said four men snuck up on him and his friend when he was on his way to the Phi Delta Theta fraternity house before one of the men cocked a pistol to his friend&#8217;s face. The suspect proceeded to [...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Two UCF students were jumped and robbed while walking home from Knight&#8217;s Pub early Wednesday morning.</p>
<p>Josiah Devine said four men snuck up on him and his friend when he was on his way to the Phi Delta Theta fraternity house before one of the men cocked a pistol to his friend&#8217;s face. The suspect proceeded to hit the student across the face with his pistol, while the other three men attacked Devine.</p>
<p>When the Knight&#8217;s Pub opened last year, students who lived in Sterling Central and off-campus fraternity houses in the area were excited to have a bar within safe walking distance. However, according to Knight&#8217;s Pub owner Pete Zachman, fights and robberies around the Aristotle Avenue area are very common.</p>
<p>&#8220;I used to live in a fraternity house back there when I went to school, so I&#8217;m familiar with the crime. It&#8217;s not really new,&#8221; Zachman said.</p>
<p>Zachman said a similar situation happened just weeks ago where a student was robbed at gunpoint in the same area. He said safety is a top priority for the bar and that he issues three off-duty cops four nights a week, which is one more off-duty cop than required.</p>
<p>&#8220;Within the perimeter of the Pub I go above and beyond to make sure not only everyone&#8217;s safe, but that they feel safe. No one likes to party at a bar if they&#8217;re worried about safety,&#8221; Zachman said.</p>
<p>The suspects were able to steal the victims&#8217; wallets and one of their cell phones before running away.</p>
<p>Phi Delta Theta President Jordan Smith said that his chapter plans on using the incident as a learning experience.</p>
<p>&#8220;We got extremely lucky that Josiah was okay. I have told brothers that from now, you should call a taxi or call a brother that you know is sober that night to come pick you up. There should be no walking in small groups until more patrols start going through there,&#8221; Smith said.</p>
<p>Josiah Devine was driven to the hospital shortly after the incident, requiring stitches.</p>
<p>He described the aggressors as four males around 6′ 1″ tall. He said the gunman was white with brown hair and the other three men were African-American.</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/KnightNews/~4/jNeInRPplYo" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/safety-top-priority-after-student-mugging/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/safety-top-priority-after-student-mugging/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Brush Fire Burns Near Avalon Park in Orange County</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/KnightNews/~3/cVzyWAkDZd8/</link>
		<comments>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/brush-fire-burns-near-avalon-park-in-orange-county/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 21:38:31 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Jacob Sadowsky</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Beyond UCF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[avalon park]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[avalon park fire]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UCF]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://knightnews.com/?p=57701</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Orange County Firefighters are responding to a brush fire in east Orange County that ignited Friday afternoon. Orange County Fire Rescue was called around 3:00 p.m. Friday to an area near Silver River Trail in Avalon Park in response to the brush fire. Officials told Wesh News the fire is spread across 10 acres and [...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Orange County Firefighters are responding to a brush fire in east Orange County that ignited Friday afternoon. </p>
<p>Orange County Fire Rescue was called around 3:00 p.m. Friday to an area near Silver River Trail in Avalon Park in response to the brush fire.</p>
<p>Officials told Wesh News the fire is spread across 10 acres and is moving quickly and growing rapidly. It is not clear if homes or surrounding structures are being threatened. </p>
<p>No other details were immediately available. Check back for more.</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/KnightNews/~4/cVzyWAkDZd8" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/brush-fire-burns-near-avalon-park-in-orange-county/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/brush-fire-burns-near-avalon-park-in-orange-county/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>UCF Baseball Starts Season on Friday, Free Admission for all Fans</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/KnightNews/~3/StQmnXJHC7k/</link>
		<comments>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/ucf-baseball-starts-season-on-friday-free-admission-for-all-fans/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 18:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Jake Rakoci</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Baseball]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Sports]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[terry rooney]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UCF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ucf baseball]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://knightnews.com/?p=57678</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[UCF baseball fans will get to enjoy free admission for the first game of the season on Friday. The UCF Knights baseball team will take the field against Siena at 6:30 p.m. at Jay Bergman Field. Junior LHP Eric Skoglund will take the mound for the Knights, looking to start off the season and three game series against [...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>UCF baseball fans will get to enjoy free admission for the first game of the season on Friday.</p>
<p>The UCF Knights baseball team will take the field against Siena at 6:30 p.m. at Jay Bergman Field. Junior LHP Eric Skoglund will take the mound for the Knights, looking to start off the season and three game series against Siena with a win. Skoglund will be opposed by Siena&#8217;s Matt Gage, who defeated Skoglund in their head-to-head matchup last season.</p>
<p>UCF has never lost an opening night game in Head Coach Terry Rooney&#8217;s tenure, with a perfect 5-0-0 record that they will look to extend. The Knights are 39-4 all-time against Siena and currently hold a 14-3 opening weekend record since 2009.</p>
<p>The Knights will have a new look to their team this season, with 24 of the 35 man roster being newcomers. It will also be the first season that the Knights are playing in the American Athletic Conference, with home series&#8217; scheduled against Florida State and Louisville.</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/KnightNews/~4/StQmnXJHC7k" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/ucf-baseball-starts-season-on-friday-free-admission-for-all-fans/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/ucf-baseball-starts-season-on-friday-free-admission-for-all-fans/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>LJ&amp;R Committee Formulates Questions for Witness Interviews in Westbrook Impeachment</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/KnightNews/~3/WjsHEOA7shk/</link>
		<comments>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/ljr-committee-formulates-questions-for-witness-interviews-in-westbrook-impeachment/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 18:46:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Cathy Telfer</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Academics]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Glide 2]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Student Orgs]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UCF Administration]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UCF SGA]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[LJR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[student government]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ucf news]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ucf sga]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[westbrook impeachment]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://knightnews.com/?p=57675</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Legislative Judicial &#38; Rules Committee Meeting took place on Thursday in the Student Government Association workroom to formulate questions that will be asked during the witness interviews in regards to the impeachment of SGA President Melissa Westbrook. During witness interviews, the witnesses will be required to state their name, position and acknowledge that all [...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Legislative Judicial &amp; Rules Committee Meeting took place on Thursday in the Student Government Association workroom to formulate questions that will be asked during the witness interviews in regards to the impeachment of SGA President Melissa Westbrook.</p>
<p>During witness interviews, the witnesses will be required to state their name, position and acknowledge that all testimony is truthful. The purpose of the questions asked in the interviews is to gain written testimony related to all charges stated on the affidavit of impeachment. Individual witness may be asked questions connected to certain events or meetings they have attended related to charges.</p>
<hr /> Read evidence submitted by <a href="http://knightnews.com/?p=57675&#038;page=3">RICE</a> | <a href="http://knightnews.com/?p=57675&#038;page=2">WESTBROOK</a><br />
<hr />
<p>The committee agreed during the meeting to ask witnesses around fifteen or more questions. The line of questioning cannot appear to be too specific because witnesses will not be allowed to speak on hearsay or speculate. Therefore, questions must be formulated in a non-leading manner. Committee members are however, allowed to ask a series of follow-up questions related to the general questions. The Legislative, Judicial &amp; Rules Committee Meeting members worked throughout the meeting on Thursday to revise and reword the line of questioning in hopes of avoiding any hearsay answers.</p>
<p>Committee members agreed to tailor questions into categories based on the three charges found on the affidavit including misuse of funds, violation of the Sunshine Law, and failure in prescribed duties. Witnesses will only be asked questions related to the charges that they are connected to or have knowledge of. The LJR Committee decided to call for an informal period during the meeting today in order to give each committee member time to create their individual witness questions. Once the meeting was called back into formal session, each member read through their line of questioning and members proceeded to vote on which questions should be passed for the interviews. A few of the questions that were passed in today’s meeting can be seen below:</p>
<p><b>Charge: Failure in her prescribed duties</b></p>
<p><b> </b>Do you have firsthand knowledge of any of the steps the accused took in order to inform the student body of these positions?</p>
<p>Are you responsible for updating the website in regard to open positions?</p>
<p>Were you delegated the responsibility in updating the website?</p>
<p><b>Charge: Violation of the Sunshine Law</b></p>
<p>Are you a member of the Pride Coalition?</p>
<p>Are you a liaison or have you ever been a liaison of the Pride Coalition?</p>
<p>When was the final decision regarding lifting of the Pride Coalition?</p>
<p>What was the date of the meeting you attended?</p>
<p>Was any matter discussed that might foreseeably come before the board?</p>
<p><b>Charge: Misuse of funds</b></p>
<p><b> </b>Did the accused have permission to purchase a rental car from Activity and Service Fee?</p>
<p>Do you have personal knowledge of what the rental car was used for?</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/KnightNews/~4/WjsHEOA7shk" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/ljr-committee-formulates-questions-for-witness-interviews-in-westbrook-impeachment/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/ljr-committee-formulates-questions-for-witness-interviews-in-westbrook-impeachment/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>“Hunger Games” Greek Week Coming in March</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/KnightNews/~3/byJMs3f-RK0/</link>
		<comments>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/hunger-games-greek-week-coming-in-march/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 03:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Cathy Telfer</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Cat 3]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UCF Greek Life]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fraternity]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[greek week]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[UCF]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ucf greek]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://knightnews.com/?p=57313</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The time of the year is almost here when different Greek-lettered organizations come together to participate in a week long period of events called Greek Week. Greek Week is a week selected from the spring semester that places Greek organizations into teams in order to celebrate the values of the Office of Fraternity and Sorority [...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The time of the year is almost here when different Greek-lettered organizations come together to participate in a week long period of events called Greek Week.</p>
<p>Greek Week is a week selected from the spring semester that places Greek organizations into teams in order to celebrate the values of the Office of Fraternity and Sorority Life, which includes brotherhood, sisterhood, scholarship, service, and leadership. The goal of Greek Week is to promote unity amongst all fraternity and sorority chapters here at UCF. This year’s theme for Greek Week is designed around the box office hit, &#8220;The Hunger Games.&#8221;</p>
<p>Fraternities and Sororities are split into twelve districts (or teams) with each team consisting of about three to four organizations. Districts are given team captains to help lead teams during the games. The pairings for Greek Week were revealed on Jan. 18 at the Lake Claire Pavilion.</p>
<p>This year’s Greek Week takes place from Mar. 17 to Mar. 23. May the odds be ever in their favor.</p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/KnightNews/~4/byJMs3f-RK0" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/hunger-games-greek-week-coming-in-march/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/hunger-games-greek-week-coming-in-march/</feedburner:origLink></item>
		<item>
		<title>Plaza on University Holds Clubhouse Grand Opening | Inside Look</title>
		<link>http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/KnightNews/~3/svwu1lXCx0o/</link>
		<comments>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/plaza-on-university-holds-club-house-grand-opening-inside-look/#comments</comments>
		<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2014 03:00:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator>Jacob Sadowsky</dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Housing]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bento cafe]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[burger fi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[plaza at ucf]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://knightnews.com/?p=57658</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The Plaza on University opened the doors to its clubhouse for the first time Thursday with a special grand opening event. Students were able to enjoy free food, music and games while touring the clubhouse. KnightNews.com went inside for a look at the new apartment complex. The Plaza on University, located at the corner of [...]]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Plaza on University opened the doors to its clubhouse for the first time Thursday with a special grand opening event.</p>
<p>Students were able to enjoy free food, music and games while touring the clubhouse. KnightNews.com went inside for a look at the new apartment complex.</p>
<p><iframe src="//player.vimeo.com/video/86670719" width="500" height="281" frameborder="0" webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>The Plaza on University, located at the corner of University Boulevard and Alafaya Trail, has 63,000 square feet of commercial space, and will be introducing more than 1,300 new luxurious and designer furnished beds into the market. Some of the top amenities include a two-story, state of the art fitness center, as well as two resort style swimming pools. Interior amenities include fully furnished rooms, utilities (up to a cap), cable and high speed Internet, water, sewer, trash and more. </p>
<p>BurgerFi and Bento Cafe are two of the tenants signed on to take a spot at the Plaza along with recently announced Floyd&#8217;s Barbershop. The Plaza will continue to announce more vendors as deals are locked.</p>
<p>The Plaza on University opens Fall 2014. </p>
<img src="http://feeds.feedburner.com/~r/KnightNews/~4/svwu1lXCx0o" height="1" width="1"/>]]></content:encoded>
			<wfw:commentRss>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/plaza-on-university-holds-club-house-grand-opening-inside-look/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		<feedburner:origLink>http://knightnews.com/2014/02/plaza-on-university-holds-club-house-grand-opening-inside-look/</feedburner:origLink></item>
	</channel>
</rss>
